sportiva.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy

Please also see our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.sportiva.com/terms-and-conditions)

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway provider's database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

The website does use cookies but does not store or track user information for any ongoing data mining or research purposes.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on 03/29/2012

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.sportiva.com

La Sportiva NA Inc.  
3850 Frontier Ave - Ste 100  
Boulder, CO 80301  
USA  

This policy is powered by Trust Guard PCI compliance scans.
